Guide to the Mister Rogers' Neighborhood Collection, 1955-2003 SC.1976.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Promotional Materials, 1971-2001; 1986-2001; VII.
  - Press kits, 1986-2001; 2.
    - Programs, 1986-2001
      - Episodes 1696-1700: Transformations, February 1996 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Episodes 1691-1695: What Do You Do with the Made that You Feel, March 1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Episodes 1706-1710 and 1461-1465: Brave and Strong and Mister Rogers Goes to School, August 1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Episodes 1711-1715: Sharing, February 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Episodes 1716-1720: Be Yourself That's the Best, August 1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Episodes 1721-1725: Giving and Receiving, February 1998 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Episodes 1726-1730: You and I Together, February 1998 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Episodes 1736-1740: Noisy and Quiet, February 1999 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Episodes 1741-1745: Go-Stop-Go, July 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Episodes 1691-1695: What Do You Do With the Mad that You Feel?, October 1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Episodes 1751-1755: Curiosity, February 2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Episodes 1756-1760 and 1461-1465: Ready to Read and Mister Rogers Goes to School, August-September, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Episodes 1761-1765 and 1461-1465: Celebrating the Arts and Mister Rogers Goes to School, August 2001 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Additional materials, 1982-1999; 3.
    This subseries contains publicity images, broader program information, memos, Mister Rogers' Neighborhood product catalogs, and information regarding other MRN-related projects. The images include headshots of the cast members.
    - Images of Fred Rogers, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Images of MRN Cast, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Theme Week Announcements, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Program Listings, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Program Notes, 1985-1992 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Pledge Drive Memos, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Product Lists, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Family Communications Catalogs, 1984-1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Childcare Project, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982-1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Production Materials, 1967-1995; VIII.
  This series contains materials used in the creation of Mister Rogers' Neighborhood, both in its on-screen content and in the behind-the-scenes work of maintaining organized records and ensuring the smooth production and airing of the show. This series is organized from broad to narrow: materials detailing the "nuts and bolts" of production are presented first, with the following subseries becoming more specific to individual episodes and story content.
  - Schedules and planning, 1971-1995; 1.
    This subseries contains the Mister Rogers' Neighborhood broadcast schedule, calendars showing which specific themed episodes would be aired on which days, and schedules of cast and guest appearances.
    - National Broadcast Schedules, 1984-1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Trolley Car Calendars, 1990-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Appearance schedules for cast and guests, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Memo regarding "Astronaut Week" air dates, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Production information and records, 1970-1976; 2.
    This subseries contains information about Mister Rogers' Neighborhood episodes for TV networks to use, lists of materials used to produce MRN and where they were located in the offices, and an informational brochure for guest stars making their first guest appearance on MRN.
    - Data for Program Guides, programs 1100-1265, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Lists of themes and topics in MRN (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - List of tapes and scripts, 1970-1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - List of MRN videos and production books (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - MRN Guide for Program Guests (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Episode logs, 1967-1985; 3.
    This subseries contains documents detailing episode air dates, lists of film clips used in the episodes, and production credit for the creation of the clips (including actors, directors, and film crew).
    - Episode topics, 1967-1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Programs 1-195, Black/White and Color Series 1, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Programs 1069-1126, Color Series 2, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Programs 1131-1194, Color Series 3, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Programs 1196-1260, Color Series 4, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Programs 1262-1325, Color Series 5, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Program 1326-1387, Color Series 6, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Programs 1391-1455, Color Series 7, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Transfer information, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Program synopses, 1967-1984; 4.
    This subseries details the guests, puppets, songs, and themes or events that are in each episode. The Episode Plot Summary folder contains descriptions of the actual story content of episodes.
    - Programs 1-22, Black/White, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Programs 1001-1065, Color Series 1, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Programs 1066-1130, Color Series 2, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Programs 1131-1195, Color Series 3, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Programs 1196-1260, Color Series 4, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Programs 1261-1325, Color Series 5, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Programs 1326-1390, Color Series 6, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Programs 1391-1455, Color Series 7, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Programs 1456-1535, 1976-1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Episode plot summaries for programs, 1001-1530 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Scripts, 1967-1986; 5.
    This subseries contains, in addition to the actual scripts, cover pages that record the scene, taping date, set, guests, songs, props and art, and other information from shooting that episode. Scripts are mostly typewritten, but a few folders contain handwritten notes and/or script additions on separate pieces of paper—some appear to be in Fred Rogers' handwriting. Some scripts also have handwritten edits and notes on them. The Kennedy Assassination special was aired after the death of Robert F. Kennedy.
    - Completion Schedule, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Programs 2-125, Black/White, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Program 1012, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Program 1085, February 1970 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Programs 1089-1090, March 1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Program 1101, March 1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Programs 1108-1110, April 1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Program 1113, April 1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Programs 1131-1135, February 1971 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Programs 1136-1140, February 1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Programs 1141-1145, March 1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Programs 1146-1150, March 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Programs 1151-1155, March 1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Programs 1156-1159, March 1971 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Programs 1161-1165, March 1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Programs 1166-1170, April 1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Programs 1171-1175, April 1971 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Programs 1176-1180, April 1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Programs 1181-1185, April 1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Programs 1186 and 1188-1190, May 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Programs 1191-1195, May 1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Programs 1196-1200, February 1972 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Programs 1201-1205, March 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Programs 1206-1210, March 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Programs 1211-1215, March 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Programs 1216-1220, April 1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Programs 1221-1225, March 1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Programs 1226-1230, March 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Programs 1231-1235, March 1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Programs 1236-1240, April 1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Programs 1241-1245, April 1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Programs 1246-1250, May 1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Programs 1251-1255, May 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Programs 1256-1260, May 1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Programs 1261-1265, February 1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Programs 1266-1270, February 1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Programs 1271-1275, May 1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Programs 1276-1280, May 1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Programs 1281-1285, June 1972 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Programs 1286-1288 and 1290, March 1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Programs 1291-1295, April 1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Programs 1296-1300, April 1973 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Programs 1301-1305, April 1973 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Programs 1306-1310, April 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Programs 1311-1315, April 1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Programs 1316-1320, May 1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Programs 1321-1325, May 1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Programs 1326-1330, February 1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Programs 1331-1333, February 1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Programs 1336-1340, March 1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Programs 1341-1345, March 1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Programs 1346-1350, March 1974 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Programs 1351-1355, March 1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Programs 1356-1360, April 1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Programs 1361-1365, April 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Programs 1366-1370, April 1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Programs 1371-1375, April 1974 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Programs 1376-1380, April-May 1974 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Programs 1381-1385, May 1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Programs 1386-1390, May 1974 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Programs 1391-1395, February 1975 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Programs 1396-1400, February 1975 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Programs 1401-1405, March 1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Programs 1406-1410, March 1975 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Programs 1411-1415, March 1975 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Programs 1416-1420, March 1975 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Programs 1421-1425, March-April 1975 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Programs 1426-1430, April 1975 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Programs 1431-1435, April 1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Programs 1436-1440, April 1975 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Programs 1441-1445, April-May 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Programs 1446-1450, May 1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Programs 1451-1455, May 1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Programs 1456-1460, February 1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Programs 1461-1465 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Programs 1466-1470, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Programs 1486-1490 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Programs 1531-1534 and Grandparents' Opera, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Program 1565 (A Star for Kitty), 1986 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Special: Kennedy Assassination, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Materials for Children, 1971-1986; IX.
  This series contains activity books, binders, and booklets intended to help parents or caring adults interact with children using the platform of Mister Rogers' Neighborhood to relate to them or help inspire an activity to do with them. Some materials are meant for children to use on their own, like a picture book about MRN or by Fred Rogers. Of the materials meant for adults, some are just activity books based on MRN, but some contain detailed information and activities meant to collaborate with a specific episode of MRN. The Plan and Play Book was the product of a specific effort by Fred Rogers and Family Communications to make children's experiences at day care more enjoyable and educational.
  - Making a Television Program booklet, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Festival of Many Things activity book, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Mister Rogers' Plan and Play Book for day care providers, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Supplemental materials for the You Are Special videotape series, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Mister Rogers Talks to Kids booklet, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
- University of Pittsburgh Book, 1974-1994; X.
  This series contains documents concerning the creation of a book by the University of Pittsburgh Press about Fred Rogers. In 1996, the University of Pittsburgh Press published the first book to analyze the life and work of Fred Rogers and the impact of his show Mister Rogers' Neighborhood. Work on the book began in 1992, and the book was published in 1996 under the title Mister Rogers' Neighborhood: Children, Television, and Fred Rogers. The editors of the book were Mark Collins and Margaret Mary Kimmel, with Fred Hetzl and Catherine Marshall of the University Press also overseeing the work. The final result included participation from seventeen contributors for a total of fifteen essays. Notable participants include Jeanne Marie Laskas and Yo-Yo Ma. The materials offer a pretty comprehensive overview of the creation of the book, except that the last dated materials are from 1994, and the book was published in 1996.
  - Planning, 1974-1994; 1.
    This subseries contains documents from the early stages of development on the book. Many have handwritten notes from the editors, along with official typewritten documents. The main points of focus in these documents are choosing contributors to write articles, matching contributors with appropriate topics they could write on, and surveying literature already written on similar topics, particularly if it already mentioned Fred Rogers or Mister Rogers' Neighborhood. The Miscellaneous folder contains what appears to be the first memo written about the project dated 1990, and a calendar outlining the main stages of development.
    - Choosing contributors, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Literature search, bibliographic records, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Literature search, sample articles, B-H, 1974-1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Literature search, sample articles M-V, 1977-1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Book proposal, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Sample contracts, 1992-1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1995; 2.
    This subseries contains letters from Mark Collins and Margaret Mary Kimmel, the editors of the book, to staff at the University Press concerning the development of the book, and to potential contributors inviting them to write an article for the book. The most detailed levels of correspondence are contained in Section 1.
    - Administrative and Editorial
      This section contains correspondence from the major players involved in developing the manuscript of the book. The correspondence traces the development of the book from inception to the near-final stages. The book was published in 1996, but correspondence stops at the year 1994. Topics include both creative choices and business matters, like arranging payment for the authors. Much of the correspondence focuses on the fluctuating list of contributors, and discussion of how to replace or revise certain pieces.
      - Mark Collins and Margaret Kimmel (editors), 1992 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Marge Petruska (funder), 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Fred Hetzel (University of Pittsburgh Press), 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Catherine Marshall (University of Pittsburgh Press), 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Contributor Solicitations
      This section contains correspondence to and from the potential contributors to the book. Many folders simply contain the standard solicitation letter that the editors sent out. There is more correspondence documenting the communication between the editors and those who agreed to participate in the project, including editorial comments on article drafts. Some of the final contributors can be inferred from the entries in Subseries 3, though some potential contributors initially agreed to the project and later either withdrew or were cut from the book. Some folders, in addition to the correspondence, contain either newspaper articles for inspiration, or drafts of the contributors' original articles.
      - Anderson, Dan, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Barnes, Corinne, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Bianculli, David, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Carey, William, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Cofer, Lynette Friedrich, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Cox, Harvey, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Curry, Nancy, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - de Vinck, Christopher, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Donnelly, Mary, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Estabrook, Carl, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Finlay, Belva, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - Flaherty, Joe, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Galinsky, Ellen, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Garfield, Bob, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Gaynard, Laura, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Gerbner, George, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Goodman, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - Guy, William, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Hamilton, Lisa Belcher, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - Head, Barry, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - Huston, Aletha, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - Johnson, Lynn, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - Koop, C. Everett, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 35)
      - Landesberg, Rick, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 36)
      - Laskas, Jeanne Marie, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Levine, Suzanne, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Linn, Susan, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Ma, Yo-Yo, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Nouwen, Henri, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Pae, Peter, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Pruett, Kyle, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Quindlin,Anna, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Rawson, Mary, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Redlender, Irwin, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Rothenberg, Michael, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Rubin, Stefi, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Sarton, Mary, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Schowalter, John, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Shales, Tom, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Shelov, Steven, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Steinem, Gloria, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Townley, Roderick, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Wehmiller, Paula Lawrence, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Zuckerman, Eugenia, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Essay drafts, 1992-1994; 3.
    This subseries contains essay drafts from the contributors and two reader's reports of the full manuscript. Of the seventeen final contributors, there are only essay drafts for nine of them. The contributors who wrote articles for the book who do not have drafts in this subseries are: George Gerbner, Lynn Johnson (photo essay), Jeanne Marie Laskas, Susan Linn, Mark Shelton, Paula Lawrence Wehmiller, and Eugenia Zuckerman, who interviewed Yo-Yo Ma for the book. There are essay drafts from Steven Shelov as well, but his article does not appear in the final publication. There are multiple copies of the essay drafts, and some have handwritten notes on them. Not all of the essays are dated, but almost all were probably written in 1992 to 1993. The reader's reports are the thoughts and comments from two outside readers who were asked to give their critiques by the University Press.
    - Bianculli, David, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Cofer, Lynette Friedrich, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Curry, Nancy, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Edelman, Marian, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Galinsky, Ellen, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Garfield, Bob, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Guy, William, 1992-1994 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Rawson, Mary, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Shelov, Steven, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Townley, Roderick, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Reader's report on the manuscript, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Research, 1972-1989; XI.
  This series contains research articles, books, and reports written about relevant subject matter to Mister Rogers' Neighborhood. Topics include how television affects children's behavior, how violent television shows impact children, how television affects the family, a history of children's television, a case study of MRN, and a biographical look at Fred Rogers. Most of the research done was professional work, but the series contains information on two History Day projects as well. Margaret C. Albert's research contains two brief mentions of Fred Rogers and MRN.
  - Television Content and Young Children's Behavior: Final Report to the National Institute of Mental Health, typescript, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Television and Social Behavior, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Prosocial Television and Young Children: The Effects of Verbal Labeling and Role Playing on Learning and Behavior, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - The Influence of Sesame Street and Mister Rogers' Neighborhood on Children's Social Behavior in the Preschool, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Case Study of Mister Rogers' Neighborhood, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - When TV is A Member of the Family, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - A History of Children's Television in English Canada 1952-1983, published report (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Appendices to A History of Children's Television in English Canada 1952-1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Motherese of Mr. Rogers: A Description of the Dialogue of Educational Television Programs, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - A Practical Vision: The Story of the Blue Cross of Western Pennsylvania, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Field Experiments of Television Violence With Children: Evidence for an Environmental Hazard (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - National History Day student project, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Unknown article and author, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Non-MRN Programs, 1975-1994; XII.
  This series contains materials from four other television programs that Fred Rogers produced besides Mister Rogers' Neighborhood. The materials are mostly promotional, though there are a few scripts. For photographs from Old Friends, New Friends and Let's Talk About It, see Series VI.
  - I Am, I Can, I Will, 1975; 1.
    This subseries contains materials related to Fred Rogers' project I Am, I Can, I Will. This show did not air on television, but parents could buy the video cassettes, audio cassettes, and books that Family Communications produced. This show was created especially by Rogers for children with disabilities and the episodes of the show focus directly on their experiences, feelings, and what it means to be different. There were two versions of the show produced for children's different ability levels: level 1 was for children with below-average language skills and level 2 was for children with average or above-average language skills.
    - Video scripts, level 1, #1-5, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Video scripts, level 2, #6-15, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Audio script #1-13, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Resource guide to materials (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Product catalog (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Old Friends, New Friends, 1977-1978; 2.
    This subseries contains materials related to Fred Rogers' television program Old Friends, New Friends. This program premiered in 1978 and focused on bringing younger and older generations together. Rogers would interview remarkable people of any age to show that "each person can make a difference in this world." The press releases introduced the person who was the subject of the program for that week, and gave an overview of their life, work, and why they were chosen to be on the show. The press releases are lengthy and act as a summary of that week's episode. Publicity photographs from "Old Friends, New Friends" can be found in Series VI.
    - Press release for season 1, circa 1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Press release for season 2, circa 1978 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Calendars (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Other Non-MRN Programs, 1977-1994; 3.